Guide to the Vassar College Buildings and Grounds Files, 1879-2007 (bulk 1910-2000)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vassar College Buildings and Grounds Files
1879-2000
1910-2000
Vassar College. Buildings and Grounds Department
72.3 cubic feet (78 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Materials related to basic service, construction, renovation and maintenance projects to the college’s buildings and property.
Administrative History
The Buildings and Grounds Department at Vassar College is responsible for the maintenance and improvement of the campus architecture and landscape. Plumbing, electric, carpentry and masonry projects, along with custodial and grounds services, are administered by the Buildings and Grounds Department. Other programs, such as Facilities Systems and Services, Project Management, Energy Management and the Service Response Center also fall under the jurisdiction of Vassar’s Buildings and Grounds Department. In addition to basic services, the department also provides materials and labor for special events, renovation projects and major construction or demolition services that require the assistance of outside contractors and service providers.
Scope and Content Note
Reports, specifications, correspondence, plans, photographs, financial information and other material related to basic services, construction and renovation projects to Vassar buildings and properties under the direction of, or in conjunction with Vassar’s Buildings and Grounds Department.
Access
This collection is open for research according to the
regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library
without any additional restrictions.
Related Materials
Vassar College Buildings and Grounds Plans
Subject Headings
Organizations:
Vassar College--Buildings
Subjects:
Architecture--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Buildings and Grounds
Encoding Information
Encoded by Matthew Thorenz, 2012.
Container List
- Buildings - Acoustic Study, 1980 (Box 1)
- Dormitory Miscellaneous, 1984-1987 (Box 1)
- Dormitory Loan Change Order Bids, Etc., 1981-1986; (5 folders) (Box 1)
- Dormitories - Electric Meters, 1985 (Box 1)
- Dormitories - Smoke Detectors, 1984-1986 (Box 1)
- Dormitories - Temporary Housing, 1984 (Box 1)
- Dormitory Computers, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Emergency Student Housing, 1983 (Box 1)
- Energy Conservation Measure (ECM) Report Forms, 1983 (Box 1)
- Energy - ECM I, III, V, Annual Reports, 1983-1986 (Box 1)
- Davison House ECM - Cycle III, 1981 (Box 1)
- Lathrop House ECM - Cycle III, 1981 (Box 1)
- Avery ECM, 1980 (Box 1)
- Main Building ECM - Cycle II, 1980 (Box 1)
- Sanders Physics ECM, 1980 (Box 1)
- Sanders Chemistry ECM, 1982 (Box 1)
- Raymond ECM, 1983 (Box 1)
- Metcalf ECM, 1980 (Box 1)
- Swift ECM, 1981 (Box 1)
- Retreat General File, 1988 (Box 1)
- Main Building - Cycle VI Bids, 1985 (Box 1)
- Main Building Cycle VI - Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
- Notice of Grant Awards - V- VI-VIII, 1984-1986 (Box 1)
- ECM Cycle VII, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
- Retreat - Nova Mechanical - Pittsfield Pipers - Altieri, 1988 (Box 1)
- [Retreat - Equipment], 1988 (Box 1)
- Retreat - Project Manuals, [March and May 1988], (2 folders) (Box 1)
- Retreat, 1988-1989; (3 folders) (Box 2)
- Retreat - Centerbrook, 1988 (Box 2)
- Retreat - Horton Lewis - Crabtree, 1988 (Box 2)
- Retreat - Renovation, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
- Pieces Selected for Vassar Views - 3/18/02, 1934 (Box 2)
- Reports of the General Manager to the President and Board of Trustees, Vassar College (V.C.) – February 1, 1956 to October 9, 1967, 1956-1967; (36 folders) (Box 2)
- Reports of the General Manager to the President and Executive Committee – September 12, 1960 to March 9, 1966, 1960-1961, 1964-1966; (7 folders) (Box 2)
- Memorandum from the General Manager to the Committee on Business Administration re the Vassar College Pension Plan and the Farm. September 28, 1956 (Box 2)
- Memorandum from the General Manager to the Executive Committee re the Vassar College Pension Plan (Non - Academic Employees) September 11, 1956 (Box 2)
- Minutes of Meeting of Committee on Business Administration on 21 Mar 1956 and Report of General Manager re College Pension Plan and Food Service dated 4/3/1956 (Box 2)
- Reports of the General Manager to the President and the Board of Trustees, Vassar College – October, 1945 - October 4, 1955, 1945-1955; (29 folders) (Box 3)
- Report of the General Manager to the Executive Committee re Sewer District. 4/26/1955 (Box 3)
- Report of the General Manager to the Committee on Business Administration re Laundry and Farm - 4/12/1955 (Box 3)
- Proposed Building Maintenance and Construction Program 1954/55. May 10, 1954 (Box 3)
- Proposed Building Maintenance and Construction Program - 1953/54, April 22, 1953 (Box 3)
- Davison House Fire Loss - Payment to Contractor, 3/16/1959 (Box 3)
- Fire Loss - March 16, 1959 - Davison House, Photographs Dated April 1, 1959 (Box 3)
- Davison House Fire Loss March 16, 1959 - Contracts (Box 3)
- Davison House - Fire Loss, March 16, 1959 (Box 3)
- Davison House- Fire Damage, Photographs Dated June 17, 1959 (Box 3)
- Seventy-Fifth Anniversary, 1940 (Box 3)
- Seventy-Fifth Anniversary - Housing, 1939-1940 (Box 3)
- Seventy-Fifth Anniversary - Budget, 1939-1940 (Box 3)
- Seventy-Fifth Anniversary - Alumnae House, 1939-1940 (Box 3)
- 300,000 Gallon (gal.) Suction Tank - 1937, 1936-1937 (Box 3)
- Sprinklers, 1937 (Box 3)
- Chapel Gate, 1932 (Box 3)
- Alumnae House Road, 1932 (Box 3)
- 1926 Construction, Boiler Room Power Plant (Box 3)
- Switchboard, 1932 (Box 3)
- New Boilers (3 and 4) 1933 and 1934 (Box 3)
- Steam Turbine and Condenser - Unit #5, 1932 - 33, 1931-1933 (Box 3)
- Power Plant - Coal Pockets, 1926-1943 (Box 4)
- Power Plant - Chimney, 1908 (Box 4)
- Power Plant - Coal Conveyor, 1927 (Box 4)
- Power Plant - GE Generating Set, Switchboard and Motors, 1908 (Box 4)
- Boiler House Alterations, 1917-1927 (Box 4)
- Additions to Heating, Ventilating and Mechanical Equipment of V.C., 1916 (Box 4)
- Sewage Disposal - Plans and Correspondence, 1893-1895 (Box 4)
- Sewer, Northeast Campus, 1926-1927 (Box 4)
- Sewer to Kendrick, 1926 (Box 4)
- North Hall, Sewer Pump, 1927 (Box 4)
- Sewer on College Avenue - Contracts and Specifications, 1944 (Box 4)
- Temperature Controls Dorms and THERM - Administrative Buildings, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
- THERM - Dorm Building Controls, 1984 (Box 4)
- THERM - Paragon Clocks, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
- THERM - Order Requisitions, 1983 (Box 4)
- THERM - Sheave Reduction, 1983 (Box 4)
- Central Heating Plant and Steam Distribution System Annual Maintenance Shutdown, 1983 (Box 4)
- Hot Water Raymond and College Specifications, 1983 (Box 4)
- THERM - Clean Chimneys, 1983 (Box 4)
- THERM - Independent Hot Water, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
- THERM - Dom. Hot Water, 1983 (Box 4)
- THERM - Gas Main, 1984 (Box 4)
- Summer Shutdown Bids, 1984 (Box 4)
- THERM - Clean Boilers, 1983 (Box 4)
- THERM - M/P Valves, 1983 (Box 4)
- THERM - Pressure Regulator Valves (PRV's) and Remotes, 1983 (Box 4)
- THERM - Chiller Controls, 1983 (Box 4)
- THERM - Repair Manholes, 1983 (Box 4)
- THERM - 1983 - 1984 (Box 4)
- Vassar College Energy Management Program Priority "A" Projects, Agenda for Discussion, 1983 (Box 4)
- [THERM Energy Resources Management Program], 1983 (Box 4)
- Energy Management Program Summary Updates Capital Spending Program, 1983 (Box 4)
- THERM Energy Resources Management, 1983 (Box 4)
- Energy Management - 1982-1983 (Box 4)
- THERM - Proposed Projects, 1983 (Box 4)
- THERM - OTW "A" Priority Estimates Costs [1983-1984] (Box 4)
- Technical Resource Management Co., 1983 (Box 4)
- Saren Engineering Inc. General - 1983, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
- Manhole Reports, August 1983 (Box 4)
- Acoustical Survey (Mr. Semmens) 1953, Sound Studio - Skinner Physics Lecture Hall (Box 4)
- Academic Equipment - Microscopes, 1955-1971 (Box 4)
- Civil Defense - Minutes, 1962 (Box 4)
- Academic Equipment and Furniture, 1954-1973 (Box 4)
- Academic Equipment and Furniture - Extinguishers, 1967-1971 (Box 4)
- Architects - Mr. Ralph L. Gionta, 1965 (Box 4)
- Civil Defence - V. C., 1951-1971 (Box 5)
- College Research Center, 1965-1968 (Box 5)
- Monthly Cost Reports - Food Service, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
- Ford Foundation, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
- Governance, 1961-1966 (Box 5)
- Mellon Program, 1950-1968 (Box 5)
- Hudson - Champlain Celebration, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
- Mid - Hudson Association of Colleges, 1962-1969 (Box 5)
- Middle States Evaluation Vassar College, 1957-1958 (Box 5)
- Committee on Business Administration, 1953-1962 (Box 5)
- Executive Committee, 1956-1968 (Box 5)
- Committee on Construction Financing, 1964-1966 (Box 5)
- Committee on Space Allocation, 1966-1969 (Box 5)
- Committee on Undergraduate Life, 1963 (Box 5)
- Proposed Summer Use of the Campus General Correspondence, 1959-1969; (2 folders) (Box 5)
- Summer Educational Program for the Disadvantaged, 1969 (Box 5)
- Minnewaska Conference, 1968 (Box 5)
- Summer Institute in Geology, 1966-1969 (Box 5)
- State Education Dept. Conference on College Building, 1965 (Box 5)
- State Education Department Summer, 1965 (Box 5)
- Summer Institute in Earth Sciences, 1960-1965; (2 folders) (Box 5)
- Summer Institute in English, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
- Summer Workshop in Russian, 1963; (3 folders) (Box 5)
- International Nursery School Conference, 1962-1963 (Box 5)
- Russian Language Institute, 1961 (Box 5)
- Annual Meeting of the Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1961; (3 folders) (Box 5)
- Summer Language School, 1960-1961; (2 folders) (Box 5)
- Institute in Community Leadership, 1960-1961 (Box 5)
- Science and Engineering Institute, 1969-1971 (Box 5)
- Summer Workshop in American History, 1960 (Box 5)
- Talladega Alumni Association, 1960-1969 (Box 5)
- Summer Institute, 1954-1958 (Box 5)
- [Division 2 - Site Work, Biological Sciences Building Vassar College] (Box 5)
- [Biological Sciences Building Mechanical Specification, No Addenda’s] (Box 5)
- Language Building - Progress Photos, 1958 (Box 5)
- Chapel - Roof Pairs, 1950-1952 (Box 5)
- [College Center Renovation], 1973-1976 (Box 6)
- Chapel - Roof Repairs and Rehabilitation, 1953-1954 (Box 6)
- Avery Alterations, 1918 (Box 6)
- Baldwin House, 1939-1940 (Box 6)
- Infirmary E. V. Anderson [Change Orders, Payments, Etc.], 1939-1940; (3 folders) (Box 6)
- Infirmary Budget, 1940 (Box 6)
- Infirmary President, 1939-1940 (Box 6)
- Infirmary Equipment - Medical, 1939-1940 (Box 6)
- Infirmary Equipment - Other, 1939-1940 (Box 6)
- Infirmary Estimates, 1939 (Box 6)
- Infirmary Faulkner, 1938-1940 (Box 6)
- Infirmary Garage, 1939-1940 (Box 6)
- Infirmary General, 1938-1940 (Box 6)
- Infirmary - Lightning Protection, 1940 (Box 6)
- Infirmary Trustees, 1938-1940 (Box 6)
- Infirmary X-ray, 1939-1940 (Box 6)
- [X-ray G. E.], 1939 (Box 6)
- Infirmary Faulkner, 1939 (Box 6)
- Blodgett - Original Specs, 1926 (Box 6)
- [Blodgett Hall Furnishings], 1928-1931 (Box 6)
- Costs, 1927-1928 (Box 6)
- Blodgett, Mrs. John W., 1925-1931 (Box 6)
- General [Blodgett Hall], 1925-1931 (Box 6)
- Blodgett Euthenics, 1926-1941 (Box 6)
- Blodgett Hall Alterations, 1955-1956 (Box 6)
- York and Sawyer [Orders and General Correspondence], 1925-1931; (2 folders) (Box 6)
- [MacCracken, President – Correspondence Regarding Blodgett Hall], 1925-1928 (Box 6)
- [Furnishings of Blodgett Hall, Euthenics], 1928 (Box 6)
- Equipment, 1926-1928 (Box 6)
- [Specification for Alterations to Vassar College Chapel] (Box 6)
- [Chapel Acoustics Renovation], 1925 (Box 6)
- [Chapel Alterations], 1931 (Box 6)
- Chapel - Public Address System, 1937-1938 (Box 6)
- Chapel Organ, 1934-139 (Box 6)
- Chapel Heating and Ventilating System, 1902 (Box 6)
- Chapel (Proposed - Small) (Not Built), 1952-1953 (Box 6)
- Language Building - Contract Award, 1958 (Box 6)
- [Cushing Hall], 1926-1927; (2 folders) (Box 6)
- Anderson, Edgar V., 1926-1928 (Box 6)
- Allen, Mrs. Arthur M., 1926-1927 (Box 7)
- Cinders, 1927 (Box 7)
- Costs, 1926-1929 (Box 7)
- Equipment, 1926-1927 (Box 7)
- Allen and Collens, 1926-1929 (Box 7)
- [Specifications for Alterations and Additions to Davison Hall Dormitory, Vassar College], 1926 (Box 7)
- [Dean's House 164 College Avenue], 1931 (Box 7)
- [Vassar College Greenhouse], 1940 (Box 7)
- [Cushing Hall Furnishings], 1927-1930 (Box 7)
- General, 1926-1928 (Box 7)
- Place, Clyde R., 1926 (Box 7)
- Service Building, 1925 (Box 7)
- [Skinner Hall], 1930-1938 (Box 7)
- [Strong Hall Heating System], 1927; (3 folders) (Box 7)
- [Skinner Hall, Charles Collens Correspondence], 1929-1932 (Box 7)
- [Skinner Hall - Heating, Electric and Plumbing], 1930 (Box 7)
- Anderson, Edgar V., 1930 (Box 7)
- [Bids Skinner Hall], 1929-1930; (2 folders) (Box 7)
- [Skinner Hall Construction - Photographs], 1930 (Box 7)
- [Skinner Hall Finishing Work and Contract Payments], 1930-1931 (Box 7)
- [Skinner Hall - General Contract and Specifications], 1930 (Box 7)
- [Skinner Hall Budget Statement and Items not Included in General Contract], 1930-1931 (Box 7)
- [Frank and DuBois - Insurance Skinner Hall], 1929-1931 (Box 7)
- [Skinner Hall Electrical Fixtures and Furnishings], 1930-1931 (Box 7)
- [Clyde R. Place Correspondence, Skinner Hall], 1930-1931 (Box 7)
- Sound Studio - Skinner Hall (Installation by Morton Lee), 1948-1954 (Box 7)
- Head Warden's House, 1915 (Box 7)
- [Vassar Brothers Laboratory Contract and Bond], 1938 (Box 7)
- [Vassar Brothers Laboratory Torn Down], 1938 (Box 7)
- [Outline Specifications For House #4 for Milton Wend], 1926 (Box 8)
- Ellis House - Wing Farm, 1940 (Box 8)
- [Griffin House Specifications], 1939 (Box 8)
- [Hopper House Specifications], 1939 (Box 8)
- [Howson House Specifications], 1939 (Box 8)
- Myers House - Specifications, 1936 (Box 8)
- Piccirilli house, 1939 (Box 8)
- Terry Cottage Rock Wool Insulation, 1938 (Box 8)
- [Elsworth House Specifications] (Box 8)
- Vassar Brothers Lab, 1879 (Box 8)
- Zehe, Paul E. (Estate of), 1946 (Box 8)
- Vassar Brothers' Institute, 1949-1950 (Box 8)
- Sunk Mine Farm Estate of Mrs. William S. Ladd near Philipstown, New York, 1951-1952 (Box 8)
- Market Street #112 - Wylie Property, 1940-1944 (Box 8)
- [115 Academy Street Sale and Renovation], 1935-1940 (Box 8)
- Property - Vassar College, 1944-1945 (Box 8)
- Property 145 College Avenue, 1948 (Box 8)
- Lisburne Grange Maps (Box 8)
- Lisburne Grange - Water Supply, 1946-1950 (Box 8)
- Lisburne Grange, 1946-1952 (Box 8)
- [Vassar College Property Records], 1940-1946 (Box 8)
- [V. C. Property - Beadle House Nantucket (sold 1938)], 1934-1937 (Box 8)
- [Specification for Faculty Housing for Vassar College], 1965 (Box 8)
- [Specifications for Williams Hall] (Box 8)
- [Wood House 114 Raymond Ave. General Specifications Alterations, Miss Washburn], 1917; (3 folders) (Box 8)
- Faculty Housing Development Proposed, 1957-1958 (Box 8)
- [Kendrick House Construction], 1926-1928; (2 folders) (Box 8)
- [Letter to Highway Committee Chairman Edward Schofield], 1941; (2 folders) (Box 8)
- Campbell, George D., Inc., 1928 (Box 8)
- Collins - Wagner Mfg. Co., 1927 (Box 8)
- Costs, 1926-1929 (Box 8)
- Furnishings, 1927 (Box 8)
- General, 1926-1928 (Box 8)
- [Kendrick Hall Stonework], 1926 (Box 8)
- [Specifications for Thompson Memorial Library] (Box 8)
- [Library Addition Shelving], 1917 (Box 8)
- [Library Tower Roofing], 1933 (Box 8)
- Library Lighting, 1951-1953 (Box 8)
- Taylor Hall (and Van Ingen) Conversion from DC to AC, 1955 (Box 9)
- [Specification For The General Construction Addition To The Library and West Wing, Vassar College], 1936 (Box 9)
- [Vassar College Library Plumbing], 1936 (Box 9)
- Furnishings, 1936-1937 (Box 9)
- Van Ingen Allen, Collens and Willis, 1935-1937; (2 folders) (Box 9)
- Van Ingen Extras, 1936-1938 (Box 9)
- Van Ingen Edgar V. Anderson, 1936-1937; (2 folders) (Box 9)
- Van Ingen Costs - Certificates, 1935-1937 (Box 9)
- Van Ingen Budget, 1936-1938 (Box 9)
- Van Ingen Equipment, 1934-1937 (Box 9)
- Van Ingen General, 1935-1937 (Box 9)
- [Main Building Alteration, Wainscotting Dining Room and Stair Towers], 1918-1931 (Box 9)
- Glass Laboratory - New England Building, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
- Metcalf House, 1915 (Box 9)
- Power House, 1933-1936 (Box 9)
- Anderson, Edgar V., 1926-1927 (Box 9)
- Equipment, 1927-1928 (Box 9)
- General, 1926-1928 (Box 9)
- [Specifications for Nursery School at Vassar College], 1926 (Box 9)
- Main Building - Structural Repairs, 1955-1963 (Box 9)
- Main Building Student Room Alterations, 1959-1960, 1962-1963; (2 folders) (Box 9)
- [MacCracken House Roof and Renovations], 1925 (Box 9)
- [Raymond Hall Specifications], 1925 (Box 9)
- [Specification for Heating - Rockefeller Hall] (Box 9)
- Williams Hall - Heating, 1924-1925 (Box 9)
- Physics Laboratory for Vassar College, 1924 (Box 9)
- [Specifications for Plumbing Work for the Physics Laboratory Building, Vassar College], 1925 (Box 9)
- [Physics Laboratory Specifications Revised October 1924, Addenda December 1924] (Box 10)
- Sanders Chemistry Lab, 1908-1926 (Box 10)
- [Sanders Physics Laboratory for Vassar College, Outline Specifications], 1922 (Box 10)
- Josselyn Hall, 1911; (2 folders) (Box 10)
- Report of the General Manager and Consulting Engineer to the President and the board of Trustees, Vassar College, 1950; (2 folders) (Box 10)
- Jewett House Bake Oven, 1940 (Box 10)
- Greenhouse Lord and Burnham, 1937-1938 (Box 10)
- Garage, 1930-1931 (Box 10)
- Specifications for New Garage at Vassar, 1930-1931 (Box 10)
- [Sports Building Specifications for Heating and Ventilation Systems Office Copy], 1933; (2 folders) (Box 10)
- [Specifications for Construction of The Sports Building, Vassar College], 1930-1933 (Box 10)
- [Specifications for Electrical System for the Gymnasium Building, Vassar College], 1933 (Box 10)
- [Kenyon Hall Furnishings and Regulation], 1932-1935; (4 folders) (Box 10)
- [Sports Building Construction and Photographic Negatives], 1930-1932 (Box 10)
- [Kenyon Hall Construction], 1933-1934 (Box 10)
- [Kenyon Hall – Correspondence and Orders from Allen and Collens], 1930-1933; (2 folders) (Box 10)
- [Kenyon Hall Construction Specifications], 1928-1932 (Box 11)
- [Vassar Sports Building - Heating. Plumbing and Electric], 1928-1934 (Box 11)
- [Kenyon Hall Flooring, Pool and Bleachers], 1928-1933 (Box 11)
- Kenyon Hall Construction Specifications, 1928, 1932; (2 folders) (Box 11)
- Kenyon Hall Electrical, Heating and Ventilating, 1933-1934 (Box 11)
- Kenyon Hall Plumbing Specification, 1930 (Box 11)
- [Edgar V. Anderson, Roofing Bond and Guarantee], 1933 (Box 11)
- [Schedule of Hardware from Chandler and Barber Co. for Sports Building], 1933 (Box 11)
- [Claim of Damages, Bill of Particulars Exhibits A, B, C and D - Supplementary Data Sheet Forwarded to Mr. Robert B. Van De Water ], 1967 (Box 11)
- [H-V-D Loan Copy Application Residence Dormitories (Stubbins) House 1 for 294], 1970 (Box 11)
- [Vassar College Residences Specifications (Official Marked Up Copy of Addendums], 1970 (Box 11)
- [Construction Ledger], 1925-1950 (Box 11)
- Easements - N. Y. State Dept. of Public Works Raymond Avenue Reconstruction, 1961-1965 (Box 11)
- Vassar College Insurance Tax Records - Alumnae House, 1961-1969 (Box 11)
- Raymond Avenue Reconstruction Special Claims For Damages, 1965-1967 (Box 11)
- Raymond Avenue Reconstruction for Claims of Damages Filed With N. Y. State Court of Claims, 1963-1969 (Box 11)
- [Raymond Avenue Reconstruction - V. C. Claims for Damages], 1966-1967; (2 folders) (Box 11)
- Easements - N. Y. State Dept. of Public Works Raymond Avenue Reconstruction, 1961-1970; (4 folders) (Box 11)
- Raymond Avenue Reconstruction East Side Raymond Avenue (Photographs, Henry Reichert), 1965 (Box 12)
- Raymond Avenue Reconstruction West Side Raymond Avenue (Photographs, Henry Reichert), 1965 (Box 12)
- Raymond Ave. - 4 Extra Views Taylor Hall and Chapel, South of Kendricks Hall Looking West, North of Kendricks Hall and Parking Lot Looking East South of College View Ave. - 4 Negatives Enclosed (Henry Reichert, Photographer), 1965 (Box 12)
- Chapel Walk Photos, 1965 (Box 12)
- Raymond and Hooker Ave. - Enclosed Black and White Photos and Negatives Starting From Vassar Lake Drive Looking North #1, Then South to Hooker Ave. Back North to Skinner Hall #23, 1965; (3 folders) (Box 12)
- Raymond Avenue Reconstruction - Progress Photographs - Views of Raymond and Hooker Avenues, 1965; (2 folders) (Box 12)
- Raymond Avenue Reconstruction - Progress Photographs, Raymond and Hooker Avenues, 1965 (Box 12)
- Dining Facility, 1969 (Box 12)
- Stubbins Dormitory (Not Done) Reports On Expenditures (Box 12)
- Dining Facility Hugh Stubbins and Associates, Inc Architect, 1969 (Box 12)
- General, 1969-1971 (Box 12)
- Distribution of Plans and Specifications, 1971 (Box 12)
- Specifications, 1970 (Box 12)
- Invitation to Bid, 1971 (Box 12)
- Steam Plant Modernization Payments to Burns and Roe, Inc, 1961; (2 folders) (Box 12)
- Power Dept. - Ash Handling System, 1960-1961 (Box 12)
- [Alumnae House Alterations - By Campbell Building Co.], 1957-1958 (Box 12)
- Boiler House Auxiliaries, 1961 (Box 12)
- Steam Plant Modernization Materials Sent to Burns and Roe, 1961 (Box 12)
- Power Dept. - Erection of Mechanical Equipment and Piping, 1960-1961 (Box 12)
- Power Dept. Coal Crusher, 1960-1961 (Box 12)
- Boiler House Etc., 1949 (Box 12)
- Unit No. 5 - Circulating System for Condenser - Estimates, 1932; (2 folders) (Box 12)
- Boiler House Sketches, 1932 (Box 12)
- Boiler House Sketches - Heat (Box 12)
- Radiation and Mains- College Ave. Houses, 1927-1928 (Box 12)
- [Power House Sketches, April 1932, February 1936], 1932-1936 (Box 12)
- Unit No. 2 Water Rate Tests (Engine Room Readings), Dec. 8, 1936 and Jan. 7, 1937, 1936-1937 (Box 12)
- Unit No. 5 Water Rate Tests (Engine Room Readings) Tests No. 1 and 2 - Oct 18, 1932 and Nov. 15, 1932 (Box 12)
- [Heat], 1932 (Box 12)
- Power Dept. - Ash Handling System Construction L. Yanko, Inc., 1960 (Box 12)
- Power Dept. - Ash Handling System, 1960 (Box 12)
- Power Dept. - Deaerating Feedwater Heater, 1960 (Box 12)
- Power Dept. - Ash Handling System Coal Firing Test Report, 1961 (Box 12)
- Baldwin House Alterations Material Sent To Architects, 1961 (Box 12)
- Faculty Housing - Inspection Reports, 1961 (Box 12)
- Faculty Housing Sites Ackerman, Know, Hayward and Pakan, Engineers, 1961-1964; (2 folders) (Box 12)
- Faculty Housing Sites Carl Koch Architect, 1961-1964 (Box 12)
- Faculty Housing Sites Clarke and Rapuano Landscape Architects, 1960-1967 (Box 12)
- Faculty Housing Sites Davies Brothers Corp. Contractor, 1965-1967 (Box 12)
- [Faculty Housing Project - Lien Waivers], 1965-1967 (Box 13)
- [Vassar College Faculty Housing Specifications (Rough Draft)], 1965 (Box 13)
- [Specifications Landscaping - Vassar College Faculty Housing, Poughkeepsie, New York], 1966 (Box 13)
- Faculty Housing - Triangle Area Ackerman, Knox, Hayward and Pakan, 1965 (Box 13)
- Proposal, Contract and Specifications for Water Mains, Services and Appurtenances, 1960 (Box 13)
- Faculty Housing Sites, 1961-1963 (Box 13)
- Faculty Housing Sites - Triangle Area, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
- Faculty Housing Sites Construction, 1965 (Box 13)
- [Specifications for Faculty Housing For Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, New York], 1970 (Box 13)
- Faculty Housing Sites Construction, 1965-1967; (2 folders) (Box 13)
- Faculty Housing Project Change Order, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
- Faculty Housing Project Landscaping Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 13)
- Photographs Showing Various Sections Of The Collapsed Platform Roof Which Occurred On The Afternoon Of June 3, 1966 - Davies Brothers Corp. (Box 13)
- Library Addition, 1960-1962 (Box 13)
- Library Addition General, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 13)
- Library Addition (Proposed), 1956-1959 (Box 13)
- Conference Reports By Mr. Hutchins, 1960 (Box 13)